Support for NPR comes from Moises, the creative suite for musicians, used by over 75 million
artists worldwide to learn, create and collaborate, available for phone, tablet and desktop.
Took every acting workshop I could
And I dreamed of Hollywood
While I read my Uda Hagen
I studied the bar
And got phenomenal ray reviews
I knew the world I was sure that was like they've done for
The critics they used to say
I was the new ol' living
I thought I'd be the toast of sun and
Home may be cow but don't but I'm a tour guide
On the jungle cruise ride
Skipper dance the same
But instead of your tale
These lame jokes again and again and again and again
Thank you. It's really great to be back at Tiny Desk.
We did play here in 2010
And apparently we did so great
Being invited us back 16 years later
So thank you, thank you for that
This next song is a song about my favorite online shopping portal.
Sadly, the Backstreet boys ripped me off two years before I wrote it.
So I still like to think this is the original.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
Are you think bad, robe, or rare?
Minced snow globe, a smurf, e-v-train.
I bought on eBay my house, this crap.
Shows of bid on Shattoners old, two seconds left to go.
Whoa, got paypal or visa, whatever the church keys sell me.
Your watch, please, I'll buy
I've been released a whole lot of songs since my last album came out in 2014, but this next song is one of the new ones
It wasn't a hit and it's not
It's not anything I would consider a fan favorite even
But it is the only song that I ever wrote that got nominated for an Emmy, so there's that
Thank you
This song was featured in the 100% completely factually accurate biopic,
weird The All Yank of Historie.
And the director, Eric Appell, kind of twist to my arm.
He wanted me to write a song to go over the closing credits for the movie.
And I wrote the song specifically for that purpose.
Really, the song doesn't make any sense whatsoever,
unless you're also watching the closing credits of the movie at the same time.
We're gonna play anyway.
It's not your new me, I'm a dirty sea crash.
We spilled all the left-of-hand, yeah, the truth came.
No skin off my only chains once they.
Pretty sure our last song that went quickly.
I feel a little naked doing this song on my street clothes
because I think this might be the first time
we haven't done this song wearing Jedi robes
and being surrounded by the five-year-first Legion
and their Stonepriop rapids.
So I don't know.
Let's see.
Let's give it a shot.
A long, long time ago in a galaxy far away, Naboo was under an attack.
And I thought me and Qui-Gon-Gin could talk the federation into maybe, cutting Vamma
little slack, but their response it didn't thrill us.
They locked the doors and tried to kill us.
We escaped from that gas, the metjarjar and bus mass.
We took a bongo from the scene and we went to feed to see the queen.
We all wound up on tattooing.
That's where we found this boy.
Oh my, my, this hereanican guy
Maybe Vader someday later now he's just a small fry
And he left his home and kissed his mommy goodbye
Sayin' soon I'm gonna be a Jedi
Soon I'm gonna be a Jedi
This junkot slave is uneven, old enough to shave
But they say he's just nine and she's 14 years
Probably gone on Mary-Hair
The song fulfilled
Frankly would have liked to stay
We all fought in that epic war
And it wasn't long, little hot shot
Flu is plain and save the day
Then the end some gungans died
Some ships blew up and some pilots fried
A lot of folks were croakin'
The battle droids were broken
And the Jedi I admire most
Met up with Darth Maul and now he's toast
Well, I'm still here and he's a ghost
I guess I'll train this boy
And I was singing
And a con guy, maybe Vader someday later
Now he's just a small fry
And he left his home and kissed his mommy goodbye
Sayin' soon I'm gonna be a Jedi
Soon I'm gonna be Jedi
Who was singing my, my the serenacan guy
Maybe Vader someday later
Now he's just a small fry
Honey lefty is home and kisses mommy goodbye.
Sayon Sunan, Ropea Jedi.
Thanks so much for watching.
Support for In-Pear Music comes from Moises, committed to ethical innovation and empowering
the creative community with tools for musicians to master their craft.